{
    "subject": "Michael_Dowse",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Kids_in_America__2011_film_",
    "human_readable": "Michael Dowse directed the film Kids in America (2011).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8233374357223511,
            "question": "Who directed the film Kids in America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.765569269657135,
            "question": "What inspired Michael Dowse to make the film Kids in America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7531976699829102,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Michael Dowse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6357877850532532,
            "question": "What year was the film Kids in America released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5907977223396301,
            "question": "Is Michael Dowse known for directing any other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5505596995353699,
            "question": "What genre is the film Kids in America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5238228440284729,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films directed by Michael Dowse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45624494552612305,
            "question": "Where was Kids in America filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23542417585849762,
            "question": "Are there any actors who have worked with Michael Dowse multiple times?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16869354248046875,
            "question": "Has Kids in America received any awards or critical acclaim?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Dowse directed the film Kids in America (2011).",
            "html": "yago_9020_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any actors who have worked with Michael Dowse multiple times?",
            "html": "yago_9020_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Kids in America filmed?",
            "html": "yago_9020_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in films directed by Michael Dowse?",
            "html": "yago_9020_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9020_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple. Specifically, document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9020/re-ranker-msmarco/53.txt states that Michael Dowse's film \"Kids In America\" (previously titled Take Me Home Tonight) is being released in 2011. Document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9020/re-ranker-msmarco/24.txt further confirms this, stating that the film is also known as \"Take Me Home Tonight\" and has a release date of March 4, 2011."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information supports that Michael Dowse directed the film \"Kids in America\" which is also referred to as \"Take Me Home Tonight.\" The documents mention Michael Dowse directing this film, thereby confirming the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}